<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Ayna Jain</title>
    <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Ayna Jain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.ayna.dev/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloudgile</title>
      <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/case-study-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/case-study-one/</guid>
      <description>Project Link: https://cloudgile.web.app Project Report: Click Here  Cloudgile is a cloud-based platform that allows developers and managers to collaborate in an agile manner. It provides essential tools such as in built chat messaging feature that allows automating user’s progress along the development of their project. The project is intended to target developers with varied experiences ranging from new developers with very little to no experience, to highly experienced developers. The minimalist design and ease of use of the project is intended to get new devs on board with agile development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJS Chat App</title>
      <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/nodejs-chat-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/nodejs-chat-app/</guid>
      <description>Project Link: https://ayna-chat-app.herokuapp.com  Project Details:  Real-time Web Application allowing data transfer in no time. Users receive messages and location across the other end very quickly. This Chat Application utilizes Web Sockets and Socket.io Library which allows bidirectional event-based communication among users. The admin users can creat a Room and the users joining the Room can enter the username and the same Room name in order to get full access to the data trasnfer occured within that Room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Tracker App</title>
      <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:07:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Project Link: https://github.com/AynaJain/Covid19_Tracker </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airline Passenger Satisfaction Classification</title>
      <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</guid>
      <description>Project Link: https://github.com/AynaJain/ML_APSClassification Project Report: public/portfolio/cloudgileReport.pdf  The factors that are examined in this Machine Learning Classifications models are as follows:   Gender: Gender of the passengers (Female, Male)
  Customer Type: The customer type (Loyal customer, disloyal customer)
  Age: The actual age of the passengers
  Type of Travel: Purpose of the flight of the passengers (Personal Travel, Business Travel)
  Class: Travel class in the plane of the passengers (Business, Eco, Eco Plus)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaFX Chat App</title>
      <link>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.ayna.dev/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</guid>
      <description>Project Link: https://github.com/AynaJain/Chat-Client-Server  This is a chat app built with java fx using synchronization where multiple clients are connected to a server and can send messages to a group of connected clients, a single client or all connected clients on the server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
